

Personal Info

- Pimpalgaon Golait, Tal Jamner, Dist
 Jalgoan, Maharastra
- +91 7218502858
- sohamerajput@gmail.com
- 1999-04-21
- https://www.linkedin.com /in/rudreshsisodiya/
- https://github.com/Rudresh-sisode/

Skills

JavaScript

Strong

Html5/CSS

Good

AngularJS

Strong

Strong

Fair Good

Strong

Good

Fair Good

NodeJs

Strong

JavaSE/EE

DataStructure in C

MySql

MongoDB

Data Science

GitHub Professional





The crossover between design and programming has always been of interest to me. I have a wide range of skills that include back-end development using open source technologies (NodeJs, Java). I'm fond of learning and teaching programming, right now pursuing Data Scientist Certification from Edureka. Actively self learning Programmer. I have live training experience in my MEAN stack certification.

Experience

2017-05 - Programmer Teacher

2019-10 Deesha Computer (MKCL Center)

Having more than 2 year of experience in Programming teaching

(done part time, while pursuing Bachelor Degree)

2018-10 - Developer

present Self Taught Developer(

I have been developing software and web app since far interlude.

I'm enough strong in MEAN Stack & Java-SE Technology.

KEY ACHIEVEMENT - Developed software for Coaching Classes and sold. Problem - Difficult to manage more than 1000 student Fees Record in

notebook.

Action - Develop software to manage fees record and send SMS to Student

Parents. (Used TextLocal API)

Result - Save time and manage all record.

Helping across 50+ student to enhance and develop their final year project.

Education

2016-06 - Institute of Management and Research, Jamner.

2019-04 Bachelor in Computer Application.

CGPA: 5.71 / 6.00. Score: 80%.

2015.05

2015-06 - Indirabai Lalwani Jr. Collage, Jamnerpura, jamner

2016-06 12th Arts in Psychology.

Scored marks: 498 / 650. Percentage: 76.62%.

2013-06 - New English School, Jamner

2014-03 10th

Scored marks: 321 / 500. Percentage: 64.20%.

Languages

English

Spanish



••••

Beginner

Software

Student Record Management and SMS Alert | JAVA SE | https://github.com /Rudresh-sisode/Student-Mangement-SMS-ALERT



Sold

Turn Your Thought |M-E-A-N Stack | https://github.com/Rudresh-sisode /newFullMen



Angular Search Value Based on user
Input |HTML|CSS3|Bootstrap|Angular |
https://github.com/Rudresh-sisode
/Angular-Search-value-based-on-UserInput



My Bootstrap Project UI |HTML|CSS3|Bootstrap | https://github.com/Rudresh-sisode/My-BootStrap-Project



Good

NodeJs using MongoDB |NodeJS|EJS|MongoDB|SendGrid| https://github.com/Rudresh-sisode |MynodeJs-Final-Application



Bank Transaction
|JAVA2EE|HTML|CSS3|Bootstrap|MYSQ
L| https://github.com/Rudresh-sisode
/JAVA-Thread



Hindi



Marathi



Additional Activities

2017-01 -

2017-01	Attend 5 days Yuvarang 2016
	Participated in Painting & Drawing.
	Received Certificate.
2017-09 -	Institute of Management & Research, Jalgaon.
2017-09	TECHZEON UNIVERSITY LEVEL CONTEST 2017
	PARTICIPATE IN C++ PROGRAMMING CONTEST
2019-02 -	Institute of Management & Research, Jalgaon.
2019-02	IT-FESTA, NATIONAL LEVEL STUDENT CONTEST 2019
	PARTICIPATE IN SOFTWARE EXHIBITION AND RECEIVED CERTIFICATE.

North Maharashtra University, Jalgaon

Certificates

2019-06	Edureka Certified in WebSite Developer
2019-06	Edureka Certified in jQuery UI Developer
2019-07	Edureka Certified in Git and GitHub Professional
2019-09	Edureka Certified in AngularJS Developer
2020-01	Edureka Certified in NodeJs Developer
2020-01	Edureka Certifed in MongoDB Developer
2020-01	Edureka Certified in JAVA/J2EE Developer
2020-03	Edureka Certified in MySql
2017-08	MKCL KLic Certificate in IT Security Support
2016-10	MCCE Certified in C Programming.

Interests

Writing Poem's.

Eager to Motivating.

Learning & Teaching.